Hey, I'm having dinner with my dad tomorrow night. Do you wanna come?
明晚我要跟我爸一起吃飯 你要來嗎？
Sure, yeah. He's kind of sexy.
好啊，他很性感
Oh, no, I'll be there too.
不，我也會去
So we'll come up with some kind of signal. If it's going well, you can take off.
那麼我們得想個暗號 如果一切進行的很順利，你可以離開
No, I just need you there for support. I haven't told him that I'm pregnant yet.
不，我要你去那裡支持我 我還沒有告訴他我懷孕了
Oh. Why not?
為什麼？
Because I know he's gonna flip out, and I hate it when he's angry.
因為我知道他會氣炸了 我討厭讓他生氣
Rachel, this is all so "Papa Don't Preach."
瑞秋，這好像 「爸爸別說教」
No, Phoeb, wait. He's a scary guy. I mean, one time he caught me smoking.
不，菲比，等一下， 他是個可怕的人 有次他抓到我抽煙
He said if he ever saw me doing that again, he'd make me eat the entire pack.
他說如果他再看到我抽煙 他會逼我吃下一整盒煙
Wow. Well, I will be there.
我一定會去
Gosh, I'm not gonna let that man make you eat your baby!
天啊，我不會讓那個男人 逼你吃掉你的寶寶
Hey, who is that guy? I think I know him.
那個傢伙是誰？ 我想我認識他
No, you don't.
才怪
Oh, my God! Monica, he's the stripper from your bachelorette party!
天啊，摩妮卡 他是你單身女郎派對上的脫衣舞男
Her what?
什麼？
Your secret bachelorette party.
你的秘密單身女郎派對
-You had a bachelorette party? -She untied his G-string with her teeth.
-你辦了單身女郎派對？ -她用牙齒解開他的丁字褲
Somebody stop me!
快阻止我
We weren't having bachelor, bachelorette parties. We agreed that it's a silly tradition.
我們不辦單身漢或單身女郎派對 我們都同意那是愚蠢的傳統
It's a grand tradition!
那是個很棒的傳統
I'm sorry. They surprised me. There was nothing I could do.
抱歉，她們給我一個大驚喜 我真的沒有辦法
Well, you could've untied it with your hands.
你可以用手解開它
This is so unfair. The one thing I wanted was to throw my best friend a bachelor party..
這太不公平了 我想幫我最好的朋友辦單身漢派對…
but I wasn't allowed. All we got was a stupid steak dinner.
卻不能那麼做 我們只能一起去吃牛排
You went home with the waitress.
你跟女服務生一起回家
Yeah, that was a pretty good night.
對，那一晚真的很美妙
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
我不敢相信你沒有告訴我
You know that the two pillars of marriage are openness and honesty.
你知道在婚姻裡 開放跟誠實是很重要的
I knew giving you that book was gonna come back and bite me in the ass.
我就知道送你那本書 有一天我一定會被報應
The One With The Stripper
本集播出：脫衣舞孃
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-I'll order everyone the Moroccan chicken. -Oh, I don't eat meat.
-我幫大家點了摩洛哥雞肉 -我不吃肉
It's chicken!
它是雞肉
-I don't eat that either. -I never understand you lesbians.
-我也不吃那個 -我一直都搞不懂女同志
-So, baby, tell me, what's new with you? -Well, actually..
-寶貝，告訴我你有什麼事 -事實上…
Your '74 Lafite, sir.
你的74年拉費紅酒
I ordered the '75. That's a magnificent wine. The '74 is sewage!
我點的是75年的紅酒 它的味道很棒，74年的酒爛透了
Why would you bring me sewage?
你為什麼要給我那麼爛的酒？
Is that a hard question? Are you an idiot? Is that why you're a waiter?
那是個難題嗎？你是白癡嗎？ 所以你才會來當服務生嗎？
This is why I told the manager I wouldn't wait on you.
那就是為什麼我告訴經理 我不想為你服務的原因
Oh, come on. Don't be such a baby.
少來了，別那麼幼稚
In case you didn't notice, that is a scary man.
你應該注意到了 他真的很可怕
He's right, though. The '74 is absolute piss.
但他說的對 74年的酒真的很難喝
This was such a huge mistake. I can't tell him, Phoebe. I can't.
這是個天大的錯誤 菲比，我不敢告訴他
Rachel..
瑞秋…
I'm gonna wait a couple of years, and then the baby will tell him.
我得等上幾年 然後寶寶會告訴他
-Why? So he can get mad at the baby? -Hey, that is the baby's problem.
-為什麼？讓他可以對寶寶生氣？ -那是寶寶的問題
-Everything okay with the waiter? -I have no idea. I went to the bathroom.
-服務生沒問題吧？ -我不知道，我去了洗手間
So, sweetie, you were starting to tell me what is new with you.
甜心，你得告訴我 你有什麼事
I got TiVo.
我有了
-What's TiVo? -It's slang for "pregnant."
-什麼是有了 -就是懷孕的意思
菲比
Well, what were you thinking asking me to come?
不然你約我來做什麼？
Are you really pregnant?
你真的懷孕了？
Well, yes and no.
對跟不對
Except, not no.
但不對是不對的答案
So to sum it up, yeah.
總而言之，對
Who is the father? Oh, no. Please don't tell me it's her.
孩子的爸爸是誰？ 不，拜託，別告訴就是她
No, it's Ross. It's Ross. You like Ross.
不，是羅斯，你喜歡羅斯
Daddy, I hope you're okay with all of this.
爸爸 我希望你能接受這件事
Think about it. This is a good thing. This is your first grandchild!
想一想，這是件好事 這是你第一個外孫
You're gonna be a poppy!
你要當外公了
That's true. I'm a poppy!
沒錯，我要當外公了
I'm gonna be a poppy!
我要當外公了
-So when is the wedding? -The who?
-婚禮什麼時候舉行？ -誰的婚禮？
The wedding. There's going to be a wedding.
婚禮 你們得舉行婚禮
Young lady, don't you sit there and tell me my first grandchild is gonna be a bastard!
小姑娘，你休想坐在那裡告訴我 我的第一個外孫會是個私生子
-Tell me there's gonna be a wedding! -February 2nd!
-告訴我你們會舉行婚禮 -二月二日
It was cool seeing you lecture today.
今天去看你上課我覺得很酷
Thanks. Although it kind of seemed like you were falling asleep.
謝謝，雖然我覺得 你看起來像是睡著了
No, I had my eyes closed so I could concentrate and, you know, take it all in.
不，我閉上了眼睛 要專心聽你說話
Yeah, a lot of my students do that.
我很多學生都會那麼做
-I've got to get going. -Okay, I'll see you tonight?
-我得走了 -今晚見？
Thanks for showing me your semiprecious-stone collection. It's amazing.
謝謝你讓我參觀你收集的半寶石 它真的很棒
My God, you must be good in bed.
天啊，你的床上功夫一定很厲害
So you and Mona, it's been a while now. How's it going?
你跟蒙娜交往了一陣子 情況如何？
It's good. It's going good.
很不錯
I mean, we get along great. She's so..
我們處得很好 她很…
-Hot? -I was gonna say sweet, but yeah!
-辣？ -我本來說很溫柔，但你答對了
She's okay with the baby?
她能接受寶寶的事？
I haven't actually told her yet. I don't wanna scare her off.
我還沒有告訴她 我不想嚇跑她
You have to be honest. Otherwise, you may think you're going down the same path..
你得老實說，不然的話 你以為你們的方向一樣…
but you're really going down different ones.
事實上你們在走 不一樣的路
I'm gonna take that book and I'm gonna beat you to death with it.
我會拿那本書 把你打死
Oh, my God, you are gonna love me so much.
天啊 你一定會愛死我了
Oh, good. Because so far in this marriage, I just like you a lot.
很好，因為到目前為止 在這段婚姻裡我真的很喜歡你
All right. I felt bad about the bachelorette party thing..
好吧，關於單身女郎派對的事 我真的很難過…
so tonight you're gonna have a bachelor party.
所以今晚 你要辦單身漢派對
I got this number from this guy at work and I hired a stripper to come dance for you.
餐廳的同事給我這個電話號碼 我雇了一個脫衣舞孃來跳舞給你看
Am I going in the wife hall of fame or what?
我可以進太太名人堂了吧？
-Honey, that's crazy. I don't want a stripper. -Will you let the lady talk?
-甜心，這太瘋狂了，我不要脫衣舞孃 -你能讓她說完嗎？
Come on, it'll be fun. It'll make me feel so much better.
來吧，一定會很好玩的 它會讓我覺得好過一點
I got you party hats and porn.
我幫你們準備了派對帽跟喇叭
Throw in my father making out with the magician..
拋開我爸爸 跟魔術師上床那段不談…
and it's just like my 14th birthday all over again.
這簡直就像 重演我14歲的生日派對
Look, I appreciate it, but it's a little creepy. I'm not a bachelor anymore.
聽著，我很感激，但它有點可怕 我已經不是單身漢了
Don't think of it as a bachelor party. Think of it as a two-month anniversary present.
別把它當成是單身漢派對 把它當成是結婚兩個月的禮物
Sure. One year is paper, but two months is lap dance.
當然，結婚一年是紙婚 兩個月的話可以看熱舞
Please, I feel so bad. Just watch the hot woman get naked!
拜託，我覺得好難過 去看看那個辣妹脫光衣服吧
-Fine, but I'm only doing this for you. -Yeah!
-好吧，但我這麼做是為了你 -太帥了
And Joey.
還有喬伊
-Thank you. Who else do you wanna invite? -Ross and Joey is embarrassing enough.
-謝謝，你還想邀請誰？ -光羅斯跟喬伊就夠丟臉了
Actually, sorry, I can't even make it. I'm seeing Mona tonight.
抱歉，我沒辦法去 今晚我跟蒙娜有約
Who would cancel an actual date just to go to a fake bachelor party?
誰會為了假單身漢派對 取消真正的約會？
I'm sorry. I gotta cancel tonight, baby.
抱歉 我得取消今晚的約會，寶貝
I'm sorry I won't make it to your imaginary wedding, but I'm busy that day.
抱歉我無法參加你想像出來的婚禮 那天我很忙
I already have a unicorn baptism and a leprechaun bar mitzvah.
我得參加獨角獸受洗禮 跟小精靈的戒酒會
I know, I know. I panicked.
我知道，我亂了方寸
I didn't want him to start yelling at me like I was some '74 Latour.
我不要他對著我大叫 把我當成74年拉飛紅酒
It's Lafite.
是拉費
The '74 Latour is actually drinking quite nicely.
74年拉飛紅酒 喝起來真的很不錯
All right, here he comes. I'm gonna tell him. I'm gonna be strong.
好吧，他來了，我得告訴他 我得很堅強
I just called a friend of mine.
我剛剛打了電話給一個朋友
I think I may be able to book The Plaza on short notice.
我想或許我可以 在這麼短的時間內訂到廣場飯店
Really?
真的嗎？
The Plaza?
廣場飯店？
Oh, Daddy!
爸爸
-Right. Daddy, I need to talk to you. -What is it, sweetie?
-爸爸，我得跟你談一談 -什麼事？寶貝
There's not gonna be a wedding. Ross and I aren't getting married.
我們不會舉行婚禮 羅斯跟我不會結婚
-I'm sorry, Daddy. -I don't believe this!
-對不起，爸爸 -我不敢相信
-Daddy, stay calm, please. -How do you expect me to stay calm?
-爸爸，請保持冷靜 -你怎麼能要我保持冷靜？
This is unacceptable, Rachel. And I wanna know why!
我完全無法接受，瑞秋 我要知道為什麼
Is it because that punk won't marry you?
因為那個混蛋 不願意娶你嗎？
-Is that it? -Yes. He says I'm damaged goods.
-是那樣嗎？ -對，他說我是瑕疵品
You nervous about getting married?
快結婚了你很緊張吧？
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
Let's pretend it's a real bachelor party, before your wedding. It'll be more fun.
我們假裝這是你結婚前的 單身漢派對，那樣比較好玩
All right. I can't believe tomorrow's the big day.
好吧，我不敢相信 明天是我的大喜之日
How's it feel knowing you're never gonna be with another woman?
知道你永遠無法跟別的女人在一起 你有什麼感覺？
Knowing you're gonna have to wake up to the same face every day..
知道你每天醒過來 都會看到同一張臉…
until you finally have the sweet release of death.
直到死神 來拯救你
You're right. This is more fun.
你說的對，這樣比較好玩
That's her! Okay, come on!
她來了，快點
-嗨 -嗨
Which one of you lucky boys is Chandler?
哪個幸運兒是錢德？
That's me!
是我
That's me.
Joey Tribbiani. Big fan.
喬伊崔比亞尼，你的頭號仰慕者
-Is that a bedroom? -Yeah, right over there.
-那是臥房嗎？ -對，就在那邊
All right. Whenever you're ready.
好吧，你準備好就進來
That was weird.
那好奇怪
-Why would she go in the bedroom? -I'm waiting.
-她為什麼要到臥房去？ -我在等著
-So she's a.. -Yeah, that's one naked hooker.
-她是… -她是脫光衣服的妓女
I love your place. Where is this guy from?
我喜歡你家 這玩意從哪裡來的？
That's an 18th-century lndian artifact from Calcutta.
那是在加爾各答買的 18世紀印度工藝品
Oh. Wow.
哇
So you're more than just dinosaurs.
原來你不只懂恐龍的事
So much more.
一點都沒錯
Oh, my God! I am so sorry!
天啊，我很抱歉
Forget it. It's from Pier 1.
算了，那是在一號碼頭商店買的
Sorry.
抱歉
You think you can knock up my daughter and then not marry her?
你以為你可以搞大我女兒的肚子 然後不娶她嗎？
I'm gonna kill you!
我要殺了你
You know, this is actually not a great time for me.
事實上 我現在真的很不方便
So come on. Explain yourself, Geller.
快一點 解釋給我聽，蓋勒
-First, you get my Rachel pregnant. -You got Rachel pregnant?
-你先讓我的瑞秋懷孕 -你讓瑞秋懷孕？
-Who did? -You did!
-誰幹的？ -就是你
Yes, I did, but it was a one-night thing. It meant nothing.
沒錯，但那是一夜情 那毫無意義
Oh? Really? That's what my daughter means to you, nothing?
真的嗎？ 我女兒對你來說毫無意義？
No, sir. She means a lot to me. I care.. I love Rachel.
不是的，她對我來說意義重大 我在乎…我愛瑞秋
-What? -But not that way.
-什麼？ -但不是那樣的
I'm not in love with her. I love her like a friend.
我沒有愛上她 我把她當成朋友
That's how you treat a friend, get her in trouble and refuse to marry her?
你就是那樣對待朋友的嗎？ 你搞大她的肚子又不肯娶她？
Hey, I offered to marry her. But I didn't want to.
我有跟她求婚 但我不想那麼做
Well, why not? So you could spend your time with this tramp?
為什麼？ 因為你想跟這個蕩婦鬼混？
Tramp?
蕩婦？
I'm sorry. Dr. Green, Mona. Mona, Dr. Green.
抱歉，葛林醫生，蒙娜 蒙娜，葛林醫生
I can't believe there is a naked hooker in there!
我不敢相信 裡面有個脫光衣服的妓女
Maybe she's a hooker and a stripper..
或許她是妓女 兼脫衣舞孃…
but she got confused about what to do.
但她會搞不清楚該做什麼
Could be. I mean, technically, she did strip. We just missed it.
有可能，技術上來說她脫光了衣服 只是我們沒看到
Ma'am?
小姐
Are you also a stripper?
你也是脫衣舞孃嗎？
No, but I can pretend to strip. But that's gonna cost extra.
不是，但我可以假裝 那得另外收錢
Okay, here's the extras: handcuffs, spanking..
這是另外收錢的項目 手銬，鞭打…
Maybe Monica's playing a joke on you.
或許摩妮卡是在跟你開玩笑
Getting her own husband a hooker. That's pretty funny.
幫自己老公找妓女 那真的很好笑
That is funny. Maybe for my birthday she'll murder someone.
那很好笑，或許我生日的時候 她會去殺人
I'll bet Ross was in on it too. I mean, he was "conveniently" busy.
我敢說羅斯也知情 他「剛好」很忙
-Do you mind if I smoke in here? -Actually, I'd rather..
-你不介意我抽煙吧？ -事實上我想…
Yeah, go ahead. We're gonna have to burn that room down anyway.
抽吧，反正 我們會燒掉那個房間
-How could you have kept all this from me? -I was going to tell you, but..
-你為什麼一直沒有告訴我？ -我打算告訴你，但是…
You figure you'd get what you wanted, then you'd dump her like you did Rachel.
你以為你可以得到你要的 然後像甩了瑞秋一樣甩掉她
Hey, I did not dump Rachel. Nor are we still together.
我沒有甩掉瑞秋 我們也沒有在一起
Can I..?
我可以…
Why don't we just let the machine get that.
讓答錄機接吧
Hey, Ross, it's Joey. There's a hooker over here..
羅斯，我是喬伊 這裡有個妓女…
and we thought maybe you'd know something about it.
我們想或許你知情
No! No! No!
不
No!
I need to lie down.
我需要躺一下
Hey, guys, can I talk to you for a minute?
大伙們，我能跟你們談一下嗎？
Listen, again, I want to urge you to push the duck special..
聽著，我要你們推銷鴨肉特餐…
because if they don't eat the duck, you're going to, and it's not very good.
因為如果客人不吃鴨肉 你們得吃，它不是很好吃
Tonight's the night of the big bachelor party?
今晚是單身漢派對之夜？
-Thanks for giving me that girl's number. -No problem. Say, who's the party for?
-謝謝你給我那個女孩的電話號碼 -別客氣，誰要辦派對？
-For my husband. -You hired your husband a hooker?
-我老公 -你幫你老公雇了一個妓女？
-She's a stripper. -No, she's a hooker.
-她是脫衣舞孃 -不，她是妓女
-Is that what they call strippers sometimes? -When they're hookers.
-他們不是有時這樣稱呼脫衣舞孃？ -因為她們是妓女
Oh, my God. Stu, I can't believe you did this.
天啊 史都，我不敢相信你會這麼做
Now, you're sure she's a hooker?
你確定她是妓女？
It's either that, or she's just the best, most expensive date I ever had.
如果不是的話 她是我約過最棒跟最貴的女孩
Maybe she meant to get you a hooker.
或許她是故意幫你雇了個妓女
Why would she do that?
她為什麼要那麼做？
Maybe she wants you to learn something.
或許她要你好好學一學
Is there anything you're really bad at, you know, sexually?
你在床上表現的不好嗎？
This is the worst bachelor party ever.
這是最糟糕的單身漢派對
-What's taking you boys so long? -In a minute!
-你們怎麼那麼久？ -再一分鐘就好
"In a minute"? What's gonna happen in a minute?
「一分鐘」？ 一分鐘內會發生什麼事？
All right. Maybe you should ask her to leave.
好吧 或許你該去請她離開
-Why me? -Hey, it's your bachelor party.
-為什麼是我？ -這是你的單身漢派對
-Which is why you should do it. -I don't want to. You do it.
-所以應該是你去說 -我不要，你去
All right. Rock, paper, scissors for who has to tell the whore to leave.
好吧，剪刀石頭布 決定誰去請那個妓女離開
-What? -I miss this.
-什麼？ -我想念這個
I don't think we've actually done this before.
我想我們以前 沒有這麼做過
No, I miss hanging out with you.
不，我想念跟你鬼混的日子
-We still hang out. -Not like we used to.
-我們還是混在一起 -跟以前不一樣了
Remember? You and me, we used to be inseparable.
還記得嗎？你跟我 我們以前老是黏在一起
You know, now it's like things are different.
現在一切都變得不一樣了
Well, you know, things are different. I'm married now.
一切的確不一樣了 我結婚了
And, hey, don't get me wrong, I am so happy for you guys.
別誤會我 我為你們感到高興
I just miss hanging out. Just us, you know?
我只是想念我們一起 鬼混的日子，你知道嗎？
Yeah, I miss that too.
我也是
I'll tell you what. From now on, we'll make time to hang out.
聽我說，從現在開始 我們找時間一起出去
You got it. Come here.
你說的對，過來
Oh, God.
天啊
Listen, I am this close to robbing you guys.
聽著 我差一點就要洗劫你們了
She's a hooker! She's a hooker! She's a..
她是妓女 她是…
Hi. We spoke on the phone.
嗨，我們通過電話
So your dad dropped by.
你爸到過我家
He's a pleasant man.
他是個好人
-Oh, no. -I better go.
-不 -我得走了
Just over here. I don't wanna miss the fight.
我只是要到這裡來 我不想錯過吵架場面
Ross, I am so sorry.
羅斯，我很抱歉
I promise, I will straighten this out with him tomorrow, in person.
我發誓明天我會親自 跟他把事情講清楚
Or via e-mail.
或是透過電子郵件
I don't care about your dad. I care about Mona. She was there and she's freaked out!
我不在乎你爸，我在乎蒙娜 當時她在場，她氣瘋了
Okay, I'll fix that too. What's her e-mail address?
好吧，我也會跟她解釋 告訴我她的電子郵件信箱
All right, I promise, I'll fix this. I swear. I'll talk to her.
我發誓我會解決的 我發誓我會跟她說
Okay. Thank you.
好吧，謝謝你
That's it? You call that a fight?
就那樣？ 你們說那是吵架？
"We were on a break!" "No, we weren't!" What happened to you two?
「我們要分手了」，「不，我們沒有」 你們兩個是怎麼了？
Thank you so much for coming back over.
謝謝你答應回來
Oh, good. You're here.
很好，你在這裡
And I was worried that it was going to be uncomfortable.
我很擔心 這會是個不愉快的經驗
No, Mona, just hear me out.
不，蒙娜，聽我說
First of all, I am so sorry about my father yelling at you.
首先我很抱歉 我爸對你大叫
But I heard that you held your own. You have to tell me how you did that.
但我聽說你控制住自己的脾氣 你得告訴我你是怎麼做的
-Focus. -Okay.
-說重點 -好吧
Yes, Ross and I used to date.
羅斯跟我以前交往過
And yes, we are gonna have a baby.
我們的確有寶寶了
But we are definitely not getting back together.
但我們絕對 不可能復合
-How can I be sure of that? -Because we drove each other crazy.
-我怎麼能相信你的話？ -因為我們把彼此逼瘋了
He was possessive, he was jealous. He could never just let the little things go.
他佔有欲很強，愛吃醋 他從來不會忘了那些小事
Trying to date this woman.
試著去跟這個女人交往吧
None of that compared to how kind and gentle..
但那都比不上 他的溫柔體貼…
and thoughtful he is.
跟善良
You probably shouldn't touch me.
或許你不該碰我
I don't wanna get in the middle of something so complicated.
我不想介入 這麼複雜的事
I get it, but, Mona, what relationship is not complicated?
我明白，但是蒙娜 哪段感情不複雜呢？
We all have our baggage. You must too.
我們都有自己的包袱 你也一樣
Why else would you still be single?
不然你為什麼還是單身呢？
I'm so gonna leave right now.
我得走了
Should I leave this open?
我應該讓門開著嗎？
I'm not sure yet. Why didn't you just tell me about all this?
我還不確定 你為什麼不告訴我？
Because what's going on has nothing to do with how I feel about you.
因為那跟我對你的感覺 沒有關係
-You still should have told me. -I know, and I was going to..
-你還是應該告訴我 -我知道，我打算那麼做…
but I thought it was better that you heard it from Rachel's father.
但我想最好 還是讓瑞秋的爸爸來告訴你
I made a mistake..
我犯了一個錯…
but it's only because I really, really like you. Really.
但那是因為 我真的很喜歡你，真的
Okay. I guess you can close the door now.
好吧，我想 你可以把門關上了
Forgot my purse. Oh, you guys made up.
我忘了拿皮包 你們和好了
He's a good kisser, isn't he? I'm going!
他是接吻高手，對吧？ 我要走了
I swear I didn't know she was a hooker.
我發誓我不知道她是妓女
Did you let her smoke in here?
你讓她在這裡抽煙？
Her ass-print is still on your grandmother's quilt. Really want to talk about smoking?
你奶奶的被單上還有她的屁股印子 你真的想談抽煙的事？
You know what, I'm gonna make this up to you.
你知道嗎？ 我要補償你
I promised you a stripper..
我答應要幫你請脫衣舞孃…
and you're gonna get a stripper.
我一定會做到
-Monica, wait. -What?
-摩妮卡，等一下 -什麼？
Carry on.
繼續
These tennis shoes are so tight.
這雙網球鞋好緊
-I think I'll take them off. -Could you not narrate?
-我想把它們脫掉 -麻煩你別說話
Gotcha, sailor.
知道了，帥哥
Just because you're not in love with the guy..
只因為你不愛這個傢伙…
-You told your dad the truth. -About an hour ago.
-你跟你爸說實話了 -大約是一小時前
-Wanna go see a movie? -Yes.
-你想去看電影嗎？ -好
Bye, Dad.
再見，爸爸
It's unacceptable! What the hell does love have to do with it?
我無法接受 愛跟這件事有什麼關係？
There are more important things than love.
還有比愛 更重要的事
You have to think about the baby.
你得考慮寶寶
You have to think about the consequences of your decisions!
你得想想 你做的決定會有什麼後果
Hey, I do think about the consequences of my decisions!
我的確會想 我做的決定會有什麼後果
Well, what gives you the right to..?
你有什麼權利…
Go to hell!
去死吧
Stupid guy on my phone.
講電話的男人真是笨蛋